vedicfolks.com 2014-04-16

# Privacy Policy

Vedicfolks is committed to protect the privacy of our customers. This Privacy Policy outlines what information we collect and how we may use it on [www.vedicfolks.com](http://www.getharvest.com/).

 If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact Kavitaa N K at [kavitaa.krishna@vedicfolks.com](mailto:danny@getharvest.com). 

Maintaining the privacy of your information is of paramount importance to us as it helps foster confidence, goodwill and stronger relationships with you, our customers. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please feel free contact us at [support@vedicfolks.com](mailto:privacy@getharvest.com).

  1. When you register with vedicfolks.com, we need to ask for information such as your name, Date of Birth, Time/ Place of Birth and email address.
  2. Vedicfolks.com uses the collected information for the following general purposes: to create your account, provide you with email communications in regards to our service, to send you Service Delivery, Newsletters, Service improvement, and Research.
  3. If you wish to upgrade your account this may be done within the application. This privacy policy does not cover any personal or sensitive information collected within the application.

### Newsletters

As part of the service that we offer you will receive our monthly newsletter. We will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters you may unsubscribe by following the unsubscribe link located within each email communication.

  1. Vedicfolks.com will not make any of the collected information available to anyone. We will never sell, rent, exchange or share your personal information with third parties other than as disclosed within this privacy policy.
  2. Vedicfolks.com will need to share the collected information in order to respond to investigation, court orders, legal process, or to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Vedicfolks.com's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  3. Vedicfolks.com reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.
  4. Vedicfolks.com will send a welcoming email to verify your new account. We will only email account holders for billing purposes. We will occasionally send out vedicfolks.com service related announcements.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

### Third Party Cookies

The use of cookies by third parties is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. These third parties use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

  1. Vedicfolks.com uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run vedicfolks.com. Although FOLKSCO Technologies Private Limited owns the code, databases, and all rights to the vedicfolks.com's application, you retain all rights to your data.
  2. Vedicfolks.com may periodically update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your vedicfolks.com's account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
  3. If you have any question about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@vedicfolks.com](mailto:privacy@getharvest.com).

### Updating or Correcting Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct or update it by emailing our Customer Support at [support@vedicfolks.com](mailto:support@harvestapp.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

### Customer Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.

### Blog

If you use the blog on this Web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these blogs, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these blogs.

### Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can email us at [support@vedicfolks.com](mailto:support@harvestapp.com).

### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

### Vedicfolks.com may be contacted at the following address:

Vedicfolks.com

FOLKSCO Technologies Private Limited

New No. 59, Nerkundram Road,Krishnan Colony,   

Vadapalani, Chennai - 600 026

By telephone:  
+91 9176777137, 9176777597

By Email: [support@vedicfolks,com](mailto:support@harvestapp.com)
